I'll see you
next time.
In order for Luthi and Robin
to get some rest and recover,
the Going Mary remained anchored.
Off the uninhabited island for four days.
After that, we set sail.
Today marks the third morning.
Since we resumed our voyage.
The weather is clear and sunny.
Mostly spring with
occasional bouts of summer.
It's beautiful.
I
made this
potato pie.
especially for you, mademoiselle.
I hope you enjoy it.
Mmm, delicious.
That makes me so happy!
Hey, keep it down, jerk!
Some people are trying
to sleep around here!
Sorry about that, cactus head.
My most sincere apology.
What, you cigarette-snorkeling dartboard?
Huh?
What did you call me? Dartboard.
Dartboard eyebrows.
What?
Lou!
We've been waiting for this! Louie!
This is me frozen.
I can't believe this is how he behaves
after almost freezing to death.
What do you think?
You nailed it!
That's exactly what you looked like!
Make sure you clean all
that up, Luffy. Okay.
Hey, Nami, is that food?
What are you eating?
Some potato pie-y.
Potatoes, huh?
I love potatoes.
Sanji, make me some.
Just how many hours a day do you
have to lie around and sleep anyway?
That's none of your business.
I'll sleep as long as I like.
Want to fight about it?
So this is pie huh good
stuff why is it called
that because the meat is
taken from the tail of
the giant beast by i
should know i was the one
who killed it who's over
a hundred meters long.
Whoa, a hundred meters?
That's amazing, Uzzah!
I did it all before breakfast.
Wait, you woke up early to kill it?
Chopper, have you forgotten who I am?
Uh...
Oh, I get it.
You're Captain... Yes, that's right.
I'm the great and almighty Captain Uzzah!
Robin!
Good to see you!
Robin, are you feeling okay?
Do you still have a chill
your treatment helped me out?
Tremendously. Thanks.
You're a wonderful doctor
He sure looks happy. Yep,
take it easy Robin Loofie's
already recovered enough to
where he's running around and
screaming like an imbecile,
but you can just relax and take your time
Hey Robin, would you like me to
make you something to warm you up?
Do you have an appetite?
I do may I have some
coffee, please? Of course.
It's my pleasure
What the heck is that
Man, this pie and stuff is delicious.
I can't stop eating it.
Yeah, oh, no.
I bet we could make some
money selling this stuff.
Luffy, come quick.
There's a frog doing
the front crawl. What?
See for yourself.
It's headed to your side.
Really?
I wonder if it's that
same frog we heard about.
Come on, Luffy.
Are you really going to take anything
that Goofy Admiral told you seriously?
There's no way a frog could
do the front crawl if...
Holy crap!
There's a frog doing the front crawl!
Come on!
After him! Aye-aye!
Take in the sails!
Stand by the oars!
Bring the ship about two o 'clock!
Aye-aye! Hurry!
I don't know why, but I get the
feeling we really have to follow it.
Sorry to keep you waiting, mademoiselles.
Uh, what's happening?
What the?
What's going on?
It seems like the ship has
changed its course. Hey!
What's the deal here?
Why'd you change our
course without asking me?
Nami, you're never gonna believe it!
We found this huge frog with scars all
over its body, and we're following it!
A frog? What?
We have to catch up to it, capture
it, cook it, and eat it for lunch!
You wanna eat it?
You're right!
Huh, is that a lighthouse?
Now, what is a lighthouse
doing way out here?
I wonder if anyone lives there. What's up?
Do you see an island?
Not really, it's just a lighthouse.
There's not enough there for
the log post to point to.
What about the frog?
Tell us which way the frog went!
Not a chance!
It looks like the frog is
headed to the lighthouse.
Frogs should be marinated in
white wine to dissolve the mucus.
Then you coat them with
flour and fry them up crisp.
Sanji, snap out of it!
If the captain says we're
going after the frog,
we really don't have much
choice in the matter.
Robin!
Let's go!
Old feet ahead! Aye aye!
Why are you all going along with this?
Hee-haw!
It's flying!
Quick, don't let it get away!
Let's get up ahead of
it and block its course!
Hee-haw!
I guess we ran ashore or something.
Nami, Robin, say something.
Are you two okay?
Yeah, I think I'm okay.
Same.
Thank goodness.
What is that sound?
What the heck?
What's going on?
Wait, that sounds like a...
No way!
Out here?
Full reverse right now!
Now turn 180 degrees!
Whoa, that was gross!
The Uncle Metal is trying to kill us!
Is it a ship?
No way!
Something that big and heavy
shouldn't even be able to float!
Hey! What are you doing?
Get out of the way!
Oh, no! Froggy!
It looked like it was spitting out smoke!
Pirates?
Granny! Granny!
Fuck me, a virus! What?
Is that true, Timmy?
Okey-dokey then, in that case, better
bring Granny the transponder snail!
It's gonna be a big pain if they call
for help when the Marines show up.
What should we do?
Here it is, Granny!
Um, hello?
Who is this?
Sorry, you got the wrong number.
She's totally drunk!
Ooh, bai-ha.
That stuff goes good with booze.
Mmm, yummy.
My name's Chimney.
This is our kitty cat, Gombe.
And that's Granny Kokoro.
You fellas wouldn't happen to
be train robbers, would ya?
My name's Luffy, and I'm
gonna be king of the pirates.
Really? Yep.
I like you. You're funny.
By the way, Chimney, that
thing's a steamboat, right?
Seems awfully long to me.
Can't imagine it getting very far.
You've probably never
seen anything like this,
seeing as it's the only one in the world.
It's not a steamboat.
It's a Sea Train called the Puffing Tom.
How does it work?
It uses a steam engine to turn its
paddle wheels and run on a railway.
Railway? Uh-huh.
If you look close, you can see
the tracks right below the waves.
The train goes the same route every day,
taking people from one island to the next.
It carries ships and packages
and other stuff, too. Oh, wow.
Funny we didn't notice it before.
Didn't you see the signal?
There's a bell ringing and everything.
How are we supposed to know?
And if we couldn't figure it out, then
that frog sure wouldn't get it, would he?
It was awful rude of you
to hit him like that.
We were going to catch him
and cook him, you know.
Oh, you saw the frog?
That's Yokozuna.
He sure was an awesome swimmer.
Either way, I wouldn't worry about him.
He's pretty tough.
In fact, that wasn't the first time
he's challenged the train and lost.
He's really kind of a pain
if you want to see him again.
Just hang around here.
I'm sure it'll pop up
That's why he didn't run?
Wow!
I thought that frog was stupid, but it
turns out he was just being super manly!
Easy for you to say you have to
put up with him all the time!
I can't even count how many
times he's broken the rail!
That's pretty crazy.
Okay, since that frogs a fighter like me.
I'm not gonna eat him
after all Who would want
to eat that gross thing
in the first place?
Anyways, after this, where
are you folks headed off to?
The Sea Train runs to all sorts of places.
There's the town of the Spring Queen, St.
Poplar.
There's the gourmet town, Pucci.
Or the carnival town, San Faldo.
They're all fun places to go.
And if you happen to
work for the government?
You can take a special
train that's even fancier!
than the Puffing Tom.
Good, then that's the
place we're going to go.
Keep it up.
Thanks, but there's no reason for us to
take the train when we have our own ship.
We'll just follow the log.
Oh, where's it pointing to?
Should be someplace east of here. I see.
Well, in that case, it's Water 7 for sure.
The train you saw on the way here just
came from Blue Station on that island.
They call it the City of Water.
They got great shipyards.
You might say that's their claim to fame
when it comes to boats their first class.
They're always coming
up with some fancy new
technology to build boats
for the world government.
Whoa Then they must have some
awesome shipwrights to some more like
damn near all of them Cities like
a regular shipwrights convention.
Oh, you hear that?
Yeah
All right,
then it's settled we're
gonna find the best ship
right in Water 7 and get
him to join our crew No,
is that so in that case? Hold on a sec
Daisy you can do it
Where's she going?
Don't know.
I got a present for you.
This is a little map of the
city and a reference letter.
Just give this to a fellow named Iceberg
and I promise he'll fix your ship up good.
Water 7's a pretty confusing place.
Be sure not to get lost.
You have a big heart, don't you?
We really owe you one.
We'll be heading back to Water 7
soon, so maybe we'll see you there.
Sounds like a plan to me.
And if you like, I can even give you folks
a tour of all my favorite Dragon holes.
Sounds good.
We'll try to keep a lookout for you.
It'll take about a week for the
log to lock onto the next island,
so you'll have plenty of
time to do some sightseeing.
Great.
Should be fun.
OK, everyone ready?
Time to set sail! Yeah!
Thanks again for the map
and reference letter.
I sure am glad we ran into you on the way.
Have a safe trip!
Better keep an eye out for all
those government types down there!
Yahoo! Let's go!
City of Meat, here we come!
Did you forget where we're going already?
What a nice wind, we might make it out
to Water 7 even faster than I thought.
I'll be happy either way.
Don't worry about finding a
shipwright, I got it all under control.
I'll get the hottest
girl in town guaranteed.
What do I care if the shipwright's hot?
I want a huge manly dude, like even
bigger than a bear, 16 feet tall!
A guy that size couldn't
even fit on the ship,
and who knows how much
food he would have to eat.
All that matters is that
he's good at his job.
If you ask me,
the real problem's gonna
be finding someone crazy
enough to go sailing
with a bunch of pirates.
Size doesn't matter.
I'm just glad we're
gonna make a new friend.
We're lucky we ran into that
train station on the way.
This map should be a big help.
All we have to do is follow Kokoro's
directions to that iceberg guy and we're set.
I see.
Ah, stupid drunk!
Whoa, looks like Luffy's art.
Okay, let's try to find a shipwright
that looks something like this!
If I saw a guy like that, I'd run!
I wouldn't just run, I'd jump into
the sea to get away from that freak.
But he looks like he might be part
octopus, so even that might not save me.
Don't you have anything
better to talk about?
Okay, everybody, since we're gonna
be at Water 7 for a whole week,
let me give you your allowance!
Oh, me first! Me first!
Allowance!
Allowance! Allowance!
Why are you hugging the shampoos up?
I know all these tin plates
may not look like much to you,
but they bring back a lot
of fond memories for me.
I almost hate to see them go,
but it'll all be worth it if the Mary
can finally get the repairs she needs.
I feel the same way.
I'm proud of her battle
scars like anyone else,
but she's taken a real beating
since we've entered the Grand Line.
The deck squeaks and we've got
leaks popping up everywhere.
Nobody wants to admit it but if we don't
fix this soon we're as good as some.
Yeah but even if we can't get a ship
right for the crew we still have
plenty of money we can do more than
just fix her we can power her up too.
Oh then let's get more cannons.
Yeah and a big statue.
Hey I think we're there.
He's right I can see Water 7.
All right men time to roll.
The winds enough don't wear us
out before we even get there.
Love.
Nobody told me it was gonna be this cool?
Whoa, check that thing out!
I didn't know they made
fountains that big!
Oh, that's nuts!
I've never seen anything like it!
And I thought the sea
train was a big deal.
At any rate, that's the station up front.
Must be the same one
Kokoro was talking about.
Still, I wonder where the harbor's at.
Inside the town, maybe?
Hey, hold on!
Pirates shouldn't sail in the front.
You gotta be more discreet.
Use the back street
entrance over there instead.
Oh, okay, thank you.
Whoa, look, there's so many boats.
Awesome, the city's floating.
Wonder how it works.
But everything's flooded everywhere.
Aren't all the buildings
gonna be full of water too?
Not at all.
The houses here were built with
a submerged foundation in mind.
Hmm?
If you look beneath the
walkway, you'll understand.
You're right.
It's like the city's sitting on stilts.
I see.
Certainly lives up to its name. Whoa! Hey!
Hurry up, dock the ship!
Whoa!
Hold on a sec!
What do you pirates think
you're doing here in town?
And you're not looking
to plunder now, are you?
Nuh-uh!
We just want to get our ship repaired!
He just asked that like it's no big deal?
In that case, there's a little
cape just ahead of here.
Anchor your ship over there for now.
Okay!
Thanks for the help!
They keep waving us off!
Of course they do.
We'll fly on a pirate flag.
Hmm.
Should be okay to anchor here, right?
Can't see why not.
It's certainly far enough from the city.
Works for me!
For all the sail!
Stop!
Are you trying to break the ship? No!
All I did was pull the
rope like I always do.
Holy crap!
If the Mary's falling apart this easy,
we're lucky we made it here at all.
By the way, they're not scared
of pirates here, are they?
Don't you think that's kind of strange?
It's because we're shipyard
customers just like anyone else.
Stop yapping and start
fixing the ship already!
They probably aren't concerned
about pirates because they
have enough security to deal
with them if they misbehave.
Bet there's plenty of Marines here, too.
Comes with the territory, huh?
What, are you kidding me?!
You mean they're gonna have us arrested?!
I don't think that'll be a problem
since we're paying customers and all.
I guess so.
Well, that settles it.
We'll see you later!
Hold on one minute, you two!
Shhh!
I need you to come with me to
take care of some business.
Hm?
What business?
First off, we're going to take Kokoro's
reference letter to this iceberg guy,
assuming we can find him.
Hopefully, he'll be able to take
care of the Mary's repairs for us.
After that,
we'll have to find a place where we
can trade in our gold for some berries.
Okie Dock, works for me.
So what are we waiting for?
Let's go to Water 7!
Okay, but aren't you forgetting the gold?
Hey!
Some pirates are causing
a ruckus at Doc 1!
What?
That's not good!
Come on, we better go check this out!
Sorry, but you're not making any sense.
Need me to talk slow for you?
So, you repaired our ship.
So, then I got to thinking.
And no matter how I looked at it,
no matter how many times I turned
our little deal around in my head,
I still felt like you were
charging me way too much.
You're interrupting our job.
Here's the deal.
I'm not paying a single
berry for the work you did.
Thanks for the repairs!
They were great!
So kind of you to do them for free!
Well, Cauliflower, you
know what's going on?
Yes, Mr. Iceberg.
Those pirates are Doc One customers.
But now that the work's
done, they refuse to pay.
Sexual harassment.
Well, maybe it is.
Listen, sir, we take
our jobs very seriously.
It's not wise to mark
our shipwrites like that.
Whoa!
COMPTON!
Oops! Sorry!
Hey, jerk!
Watch where you swing that thing!
You just knocked out a...
Oops. Sorry.
Hey, you punks trying to pick a fight?
Who do you think you are?
Oh, yeah.
We haven't had a chance to
test-fire that cannon, have we?
No, not yet.
Damn you!
You won't get away with this!
We'll be back just when!
You're out, shipwreiter.
This is what happens when you try to
pull that pirate crap around here.
Maybe we should trade in the
gold before anything else.
That's boring.
I want to go to the shipyard.
It might not matter to you, but I'd feel
nervous walking around a crowded city!
dragging a giant bag
of treasure behind me.
If we trade it, we'd still
be dragging berries around.
I know, but it'll be a lot smaller
so people won't notice it as much.
I mean, what if we run into thieves?
Ha!
We are thieves!
Well, that's true.
But if we cash it in, you won't be
the only one carrying the money.
I don't know if I like the sound of that.
It's almost like you don't want
me taking care of the gold.
Yep.
Only you could lose that much gold.
He already forgot it once today.
You guys don't trust me,
your own captain? Nope.
Aw, hey, that really hurts my feelings.
I don't know if I can keep
sailing with a crew that...
Wait, what's that?
Huh, that's funny.
Is that the only entrance to the city?
What's a rental bull shop? Beats me.
Obviously, they must rent out something.
Yeah, but what's a bull?
I don't know.
Like a bulldog?
Oh, that can't be right.
Excuse me, we'd like to rent some bulls.
Find out what they are first.
Hm?
Hi, looking for some bulls, you said?
How many people? We've got three.
What kind would you like?
There's three ranks,
Yagada, Rabaka, and King.
For your little group, I'm thinking
two Yagadas will do just fine.
Give me one rare and one well done.
You don't know what you're saying, do you?
Oh?
You followed a log to get here? Yep.
That's quite an achievement, but
if you're not from around here,
this is probably the first time
you've ever heard about bulls.
Well, to make a long story short,
there they are, Yagada bulls.
You can find them all over town.
As you can see, it's a type of fish that
swims with its head above the water.
Since the whole city is flooded, we
have a lot more canals than walkways.
Because of that,
pretty much everyone around here
uses the bulls in their daily life.
If you want to go sightseeing,
you'll need one, too.
So they use the bulls to
pull those little boats?
Actually, the boat parts
mounted on their back.
In other words, it's not much different
than riding horseback on land.
Go ahead and take a look at the bullpen
over there if you want to pick one out.
They don't bite.
It'll be 2,000 berries for
two two-passenger yogatas.
Aw, they're cute.
They even look like horses.
That's gross!
What's wrong with you, horsefish?
Ha!
Since that one seems to like
you, I'll mount him for you.
Is he all right carrying heavy stuff?
Yeah, these guys are built for power.
The people here use them
for moving all the time.
That's a big bag.
Can I ask what's inside? Gold.
That's a good one.
Well, whatever it is, it'll be okay. See?
Whoa, gimme! Yeah, right!
I guess he thought it was
worth asking, at least.
This is why I said I don't
trust you with the money!
I had to show him.
He didn't believe me.
Wow, I sure wasn't expecting that.
Like I said, that'll be one million
berries for two yogurtables.
Don't try to change the price on us!
Speaking of gold, do you know
where we can get ours cashed in?
Well, there's quite a few places, but
you'd probably clean them all out!
trying to trade in that
much treasure in one shot.
If I were you, I'd check out
downtown on the Shipbuilders Island.
We're not really familiar with the area.
Think you could give us some directions?
It's right over there.
Here, take this.
Oh, a map!
Thanks for the help!
Hey, we could find a
shipyard downtown too, right?
Yep, best one in the world.
That'll be perfect!
We can head straight to the shipyard
soon as we trade in our gold!
Well, you're not going to
hear any complaints from me.
As long as the Mary gets
repaired, I'll be happy.
Then we'll find a ship ride!
Ha!
Oh, man, I can't wait!
Well? Shall we? Yeah!
Go, Yakara!
See you later!
Thanks for your business
and have a safe trip!
Downtown!
Full speed ahead!
Yahoo!